so I don't do a formal intro I just say
hey man how are you guys something
really fast before I start how does my
moustache look it's pretty good it's
it's solid really it's like you're not
trying like it's just a natural I'm
trying really hard but it looks like
you're not trying
that's probably actually not good oh
okay cuz I want it no no I can't grow a
moustache I can't grow a good facial
hair I just wanted to make sure that it
debuted well because I haven't really
had shown my moustache to that many
people
well now we can see I guess I did a
mustache for a while and it was like I
was genuinely trying I was like I was
like I wonder like I don't know what's
it like I've always had a beard a facial
hair like consistent whatever and I was
like shaved the [__] rest of it in my
girlfriend not a fan not if like it's
like she wouldn't take anything I was
saying seriously dude girls not like
mustaches no mine
I like mustaches no well don't worry cuz
mine is very juvenile looking I say
mustache I will promise
I say mustache but what I really mean is
just I look like I'm 15 again basically
it looks good man thank you
ain't so bad at all here so six feet
cheers from across the table you got oh
if you need another proof yeah but you
out there I did thank you my love what a
sweetie see you see that the patriarchy
already taken over I feel so bad now I
should have gotten up you got in the
beer people I'm gonna be canceled for
this cancel culture oh all right so my
god give them some [__] to cancel um Joe
I've had comments on this whole cancel
culture thing it's really funny to me I
am crazy
it's [__] ridiculous I just found out
that renowned mustache enthusiast Adolf
Hitler was a Nazi and childhood
shattered canceled that's basically what
it is though is people going back and
you're you're going back into something
where we already all know about this his
fan base is cool with it just whoever
we're cancelling here and we've all
decided we're cool about it
you're not even his demographic how
exactly are you gonna cancel him I'm
offended
for those people yeah like you were
never gonna go to his show you were
never gonna buy his CD or his comedy
special you were like keep doing what
you were doing and continue to not
support that person but I don't really
understand the whole and it's usually
something for like um like satire parody
they're trying to cancel that Joji kid
you know him yeah the truck canceled
never about that because the filthy
Frank thing they're the young kids are
just now finding out that he is that
filthy Frank character and I guess he
probably said a lot of um like he had a
lot of Japanese characters Yee is
Japanese so I don't know where we are on
like can we make fun of ourselves at
this point I feel like I'm still allowed
to make Hispanic jokes and Middle
Eastern jokes I don't do it if it's out
of taste but you can't go back six years
in someone's YouTube Twitter history and
it's completely parody when it's satire
clearly and you're gonna try to get mad
about it now it's it's weird okay so so
I mentioned this so think about Kevin
Hart for example like what happened to
him like they told the joke they pulled
a joke that was just [__] hilarious
like nobody really thought much about it
like what was it like he was saying he's
gonna throw it all house at his kid or I
don't know if it was hilarious but as a
comedian it was a joke it was a joke and
you have to respect that like you have
to let someone attempt to make a joke
it's not someone saying this is my
belief this is my opinion and he said if
my son tried to play with dolls I will
beat his I'll beat him with a dollhouse
or it's something like that or if my son
I believe he said if my son is it turns
out to be Gayle Stabbin right but like
it was a bad joke but it was an attempt
at a joke and you also have to
understand this is before people knew
what Twitter was what political
correctness like what this was all gonna
be we didn't know what we could joke
about we didn't know who was gonna see
this years later I don't think people
really understood context back then like
someone is reading this and they don't
know you're joking I don't think people
really even though you got that I don't
think people really comprehend like that
things changed to like that we like just
as a [__] species in a society we we
adopt and grow and and we learn like
that is kind of [__] up to say yeah
like so in comedians are the ones who
are finding that edge it's their job
it's a job to find the edge
like we we can't just [__] pull up
old [__] people said and like you mean
this now we have to be allowed to say
that right we because we are joking if
we are not allowed to say things no one
is I get it if you're gonna get mad at
somebody because they release this long
manifesto and they're just an actor and
does it okay sure
but if you don't let the people whose
job it is to joke and not be taken
seriously not be taken serious if you
don't let them do that no one is safe
literally that is the last bastion
that's the last pillar of freedom of
speech that we have is JK and if you
take JK away what can you say there's
literally nothing else you can do like
yeah I don't think see I'm such an
advocate of that too because I just I
like like the philosophy side of things
I love studying philosophy cuz I feel
like it points out it's like the
elaborated more overly serious for no
reason version of comedians like it's
like here's what's crazy that we do and
why we do it and it almost like wakes
people up to the reality of like oh yeah
I was taking nothing too seriously
exactly but I think it's it's one of the
most important things like like the
canceled culture the D platforming thing
like when I started seeing it like if
probably I was consuming massive amounts
of Joe Rogan and having his same
opinions but yeah I was like [__] lactam
this is bad for society but really
though it is like it can't happen and I
think when it started happening you
start actually like there was some
people who took a [__] like there's some
people who took the hit you know but I
think more comedians kind of started
stepping up a little more like they
started like breaking the wall more like
I remember when when Dave Chappelle I
mean as more recent special was like you
know what sucks y'all [__] yes
is like talking about the audience and
my kid just started going off from that
point yeah that's um that's that's a new
thing
I almost count that special as
performance art and not even stand-up
comedy because there's so much nuance in
to even just down to the way he was
dressed the way the things he chose to
talk about I look at that as basically
I'm going to get up here on this not to
compare him to Christ but like I'm going
to totally do it right now
I'm gonna get up here on this comedy
crucifix and I'm gonna say all the
things
Deshea I'm gonna say them and I'm gonna
be wearing a janitor's outfit yeah and
uh cancel me and it's not gonna work and
now that leaves the lane up for people
like me to wear like okay whoo I can
breathe I can say this thing I'm just
joking even though it's not fully like
that yet but it's getting there but um I
don't know I when you start to take like
what comedians Dave Chappelle especially
he is a barometer when we take something
we joke about it right you can take the
power away from it and you can get
people to look at it from a new
perspective right you can get people to
laugh at themselves but if everyone is
afraid to make a joke everyone is can
kind of continue to stay in the same
patterns of thoughts mm-hmm because you
can't ever look at yourself and go like
you were saying oh ha that was silly why
would I think that like nope we'll just
keep saying things that we agree with
like we were saying before we started
recording I saw someone comment you
don't need anyone around you who has a
separate opinion from you that is the
most aggressive yeah like that's [__]
and it's kind of that if you don't allow
somebody to joke about something that
you don't agree with you're just going
to continue the history is going to
repeat itself we're never gonna realize
hypocrisy and things it's our job to
point out hypocrisy as a comedian how
can I ever point out how somebody's
doing something stupid if I'm gonna get
in trouble for it how are you guys gonna
realize yeah I mean it's it's
interesting to think cuz you know
comedians you can think back just in my
head I'm like okay jesters like that's
what that's what they were before right
like okay you but but it seems like in
movies and I don't know a ton about
jesters at all so it could be pulling
sentiment but movies it's like like you
say the funny things but there's always
this like kind of little edge we're back
in the day you can't like make fun of
the Queen no like don't [__] make fun
of the Queen that's an interesting
comparison to draw because if a gesture
did something that a queen or a king
didn't like it was off with your head
yeah and that's how it's becoming now
yeah in what an insane reality that we
can't [__] live in that are you out
of your mind like that's crazy but so at
the same time that these sort of things
happening and like I said there's a lot
of people who like you know the legends
have kind of stepped into the light
lately of sorts or are starting to or
whatever may be missing it but at the
same time there's also a new form of
comedy social media there's an
just comedians on social media there's
like random [__] who are just
like hateful bastards and they make
hilarious memes yeah like we have new
forms of comedians now - there's an
there's apps that are coming out that
are creating new forms of comedy just
from being born as an app like tic toc
you know that was never a form of comedy
before mime dancing in front of a and
then fly away like I don't know you know
no that's completely new so like every
time an app comes out now we have a
whole new realm of comedy that was born
like a whole new genre of comedian that
is live and I think like I was gonna say
earlier in terms of the canceled culture
and like um it seems to go on waves
I do think it is unhealthy but I do
think we need it the internet used to be
a really dark mene mene and it's still
very dark and mean but it was not a
friendly place for overweight people
LGBT people the internet in 2011 was
bully central like you were going to get
bullied into suicide in 2011 if you were
gay overweight odd in any different way
I've recently gone on a little bit of a
youtube rabbit hole during this
quarantine thing and I kind of got to
look into what social media was like in
2011 in 2012 because as I was saying I
wasn't around for that I swore off
social media at that time and it was a
really mean place and I can see why that
wave crested of political correctness
because it was so politically incorrect
you were allowed to say anything about
anybody that the wave crested and now we
have too much of it and just like with
too much of anything
it's an ebb and flow now everyone is
starting to realize like okay we can't
be this stringent about every single
little thing but there is a lot of good
aspects that have come from canceled
culture and I'm not mad at a lot of it I
think that body positivity and things
like that are great and I'm glad that if
you try to say some homophobic remarks
on the Internet
there is a gang of blue haired blue
haired girls that are going to post your
picture and everyone's gonna know about
your homophobia leave so I like that
right I don't like this if it doesn't
fit my agenda ruin this man's life yeah
that's fine that's what I don't like or
woman's life yeah like the lady who got
off the plane from that go in Africa
hope I don't get AIDS don't worry I'm
white
Richard Branson or the Bronson guy
k-member his name he's the guy who wrote
men who stare at goats he wrote a book
about her where this woman and this is
like 2013 before she really realized you
can't say that she is about to get on a
plane to Africa and does a stupid tweet
she has probably 30 followers about to
go to Africa hope I don't get AIDS oh
don't worry I won't I'm white she has 30
followers she's a nurse or something
she's probably not thinking much this
woman gets on a plane no we're playing
no phone on a plane when she steps off
that plane her life is over she has been
cancelled and completely stoned in the
public square by the time she steps off
that plane and her life changed in a
matter of three hours and that can
happen to anybody well you don't have to
be famous well so ok so take apart that
situation they're like holy [__] like I
mean obviously I feel bad for her like
we're OK but so so in this age situation
she said something that would be
perceived as racist very racist no but
but so how do we solve that how do we
like how do we like [__] and hook her up
to a lie-detector test and be like are
you racist though like are you a threat
to other people's way of life are you
it's up to the court of public opinion
and the court of public opinion is not
nice if you're asking me someone who is
very trained in the art of nuance and
context because I tell a lot of very
polarizing jokes I see that you were
joking you didn't say hey guys black
people are the cause for AIDS and the
only ones who get it I'm white and proud
you didn't say that
you made a joke and I can tell you were
trying to joke so it was distasteful it
wasn't really funny at all
I forgive you the court of public
opinion does not agree with me you are
racist for even thinking that can either
say it like it like it's the words it
doesn't matter who you are these words
if you say them that tweet now defines
you as a person yeah I don't care how
much charity you've done in your life to
the court of public opinion I'm not
saying it's right but to them you're
done that's it and it's like I am going
to Africa to work with Doctors Without
Borders to save it but I don't care if
you
is that what she was doing actually was
Kota BIM I don't know probably not yet
but still it could have been that same
exact now people would not care that's
the other thing in minefield it's just
that it's crazy how close it is we're
just talking about like the Queen's I
can't [__] this guy off with this
jesters head oh dude I'm glad that I so
we were saying earlier myspace was the
saying 2008 2009 I was still in high
school I was probably a senior I was
about 18 19 at the time and Facebook
reared its ugly little mug and everyone
was like oh there's this new social
media I said you know what this stuff
makes me feel weird when I'm on it and I
don't really think I liked it and I did
not get on the internet or own a
smartphone from 2008 to 2016 at all I
would get on once in a while to like
look up a YouTube video or whatever you
know what I mean but even though I was
just like looking up like awesome fails
very 2020 and I'm I'm glad that I did
not have the internet back then I'm also
not glad because I think I would be much
further in my career at this point if I
did have it but the things that I would
have said and I would have thought and I
would have believed back then I was a
very different person I'm glad that I
got to go through my 18 to 24 year old
stage of having all these stupid ideas
and dumb jokes and all these things I'm
glad that I got to do that in private
and no one's ever gonna be able to go
back and look at something stupid I said
when I was 19 because that would [__]
scare the [__] out of me I just I cast
well dude I have so I've been someone
who's been [__] thoroughly addicted
social media have always liked social
media I've liked MySpace I was like I'm
gonna be the eye who lays on the train
tracks and gets my photo taken and like
do you know what's funny is like I got
reassurance I was talking about it's
another podcast and in my friend
Mackenzie was like no no you were cool
you were cool I was like other people
saw me who didn't know me in person but
on MySpace anyway so like I've always
been in the [__] into social media
and I never like I don't even know like
I didn't ask myself like why I was just
so into it but um I feel like it was
such an addiction that I didn't know
that I have yeah is simple [__]
dopamine pleasures like it like I don't
even know what I'm consuming dude and I
didn't really know that and I
did I worked in a lumber mill for five
years and essentially what I did was the
job itself was easy as cake and if
you're good at it you don't touch it
but you you hit this button in this
button and as long as you got everything
set up good if nothing [__] up you
don't have to get out that console's
happening row i sat there on my phone I
would sit there and I would I would hit
the button and then less than a minute
would go by and I would pull up the
exact same apps refresh them and see if
anybody say anything new and like I
never I would haven't stopped myself to
be like the [__] am i doing like why am
i consuming this why do I want to know
what these people are saying it takes a
lot to step back and look at yourself
from the lens of what the [__] what do
you do you think that could you do like
an open comparison between like maybe
what other people experience like even
compare us not gonna hurt my friends
with anything either but like do you
feel what do you feel that you maybe got
that I didn't get her like what what did
I take away from myself from being what
did I get from being on social media or
not being on social from not being on
social media I do I know that there are
things that are way below I saw this
this artist that I really love this
tattoo artist did this on somebody I
miss my pre-internet brain this whole
FOMO this anxiety that I have this
where's my phone when I leave a place
when I go a place when I go to the
bathroom who's messaging I did not have
that I was exactly where I was even
though I was still dealing with mental
health issues I still was depressed I
still wasn't completely happy in life I
was where I was and that's where I was
and I wasn't supposed to be anywhere
else there was no looking at my phone
like what's this I didn't have that at
all I miss that so much
I miss not worrying about being
somewhere that I'm supposed to be like I
was exactly with who I was with I was
talking to that person you would never
have a conversation with me where oh
yeah uh-huh that would never happen it
wasn't it realm and I the thing that I
didn't get from it was validation for my
art I needed that and I wasn't getting
it well yeah but that's not for
everybody not everybody is a creator not
everybody needs validation on the
internet but I literally was living in a
realm of is this even funny
am I even good at singing am i
delusional because I try not to be
narcissistic
and I really had this crazy battle
before I got an Internet of I didn't
even want to post stuff cuz I was like
am i [__] crazy
like am i delusional because I didn't
want to just think like oh wow I'm
really really funny and just do it and
the internet gave me reassurance of
you're not crazy your belief in yourself
is founded because other people believe
in you just as much as you do
it's showable and it's provable so I
didn't have that validation I felt
really alone in the world but I also
felt so relaxed calm without the
internet I was fine I did there was
nothing to check check that was the only
thing I had to check with my poll think
about FOMO like just that word like you
know it's kind of like a it's a
laughable like joke where they think
about the little blue the Bluebird for
Twitter is like oh it's cute little
Bluebird but like Twitter is like you
can ruin your [__] life by saying
something like it's these little dorky
things FOMO we have that word we hear
that it's kind of like said in pop
culture but like [__] man it's a real
thing like people feel genuine like my
life sucks my house sucks I hate
everything cuz I'm not with these people
they didn't invite me I'm not being a
part of this thing I'm missing out on
this I didn't hear the hottest music I
didn't see the newest thing I'm missing
out on joke so that I don't get because
people are talking about the memes they
just saw that are new like it's it's a
you know fear of missing out FOMO but
it's it's another way for being in
physical reality for all of a sudden our
fear body are like old limbic reptilian
brain to be activated I think I think
that it's something that just like with
all things just like with all drugs
you can use it medicinally and it can be
a drug the fact that it can be an
addiction the fact that I can get on
here and even though my life is in
shambles I am sleeping on a box spring I
that not to say that any of this true it
totally is I'm drinking mouthwash every
day my life is terrible but at least I
am doing well on the internet or
whatever that can be really really
detrimental but if you use it as a tool
to like be motivation yeah I get
everything in my life is not great right
now but the Internet is a place where I
get a validation and it makes me feel
good
also you need to be changing those
things in your life that aren't good
like that's great that you get
validation from the internet
but get a good bed you know strive
offspring strive for something more and
get that validation from the Internet
don't let that validation from the
Internet Beamer and all be all I think I
get noticing that it's validation is the
biggest thing yes like a lot of a lot of
us don't know that we're seeking
validation like me for example for many
years I didn't realize I'm just I'm just
need approval of other people I need to
like think of something that's gonna get
likes rather than like what I really
[__] want to say like what do I
really like like now when I post to
Instagram I get sometimes [__] 14
likes but it's something that I
genuinely [__] like now man and it's
not like but back then I could post the
coolest outfit then I like you know took
took awhile to do the lighting and I
blob I and half a cool background and I
get like [__] 170 likes but I feel
like I never took the time from like
high school to whenever to be like what
are likes what am i doing why do I want
them they're just it's a playing a
[__] slot machine getting a little
themeing ting ting and it you realize
it's like a breeding ground for not good
feelings that you're like editing this
picture and everything and you're not
like oh I look good you're like oh I
look better if I do this
yes exactly you're not like oh man great
I look so cool in this outfit you're
like man I hope my shoes are new enough
and I hope this filter works I'll make
myself better and then you get the
validation from this character that
you've developed but that's not real
that's not you that's not real that's
not someone saying hey you're a good
person I've seen how you act with your
friends and I think you're beautiful for
that that's not the same as going hey
you have a sick outfit that's all
superficial so you might get validation
from that but it's not true and I think
people know that I went to the internet
for validation I am very aware that's
what I was seeking so I don't really
have a good spectrum on that maybe
because I am very comfortable with the
fact that I want you to tell me that I
am funny I want you to tell me that I am
attractive I need that and I'm okay with
that but I don't define myself by that
because I have this whole definition of
myself that I had before I even had
social media but it's just it's this
it's just like drugs dude it is it's
just like drugs man like opiates
literally can be a helper or a harm
you'd choose how you want to use it
right it just depends I feel bad for
people who I can tell that social media
is the only like last it's all that
they're holding on with and they're not
even using it properly like your your
your thing that's keeping you going is
anger and reserve and resentment and
bitterness and narcissism when you could
be using social media to get positive
validation by say like how you do when
someone you make someone else feel good
hmm
how about make someone else feel good
that's gonna make you have some [__]
validation that you can't even
understand from getting a compliment on
your outfit right like you can use the
internet for good or you can use it for
evil
what kind of validation you want I want
validation from validating you right you
know and also tell me I'm cute also hit
like just saying I think social media is
cool like you know I can brain fart at
exactly what I thought I was going to
say something massively important we
does that we haven't even smoked I took
a hit I took the hit a weed you right
there it is a just for you buddy oh my
god some bounds and some weeds I've been
smoking weed since the fourth grade can
you believe that yo you know what's
funny is I probably like okay well I met
you originally we used to skateboard
together back in the day this is true
twelve thirteen I'm trying to think I
definitely didn't smoke weed I probably
thought smoking weed was super square
but it was because my dad just super
loved meth and he also did weed so I was
just like drugs
not cool bad right but then I but then
you know what's [__] funny and
probably traumatizing is by the time I
turned 15 I was hanging out at my dad
and we smoked weed together he wasn't
doing math back you know he was cool
when you were how old 15 okay yeah so
that's when my family started smoking
with me too my grandma handed me the
pipe of 14 around that age my grandma
was also watching as my dad just get
stitches yeah I've been smoking a good
amount of weed during quarantine it's
it's funny like like it's of course
a habit and addiction it's something
that I'm like okay like I definitely do
if I'm in a situation and I'm not stoned
I'm like hanging out my backyard I'm
like mmm I should go take a bong rip
because playing with my papi or mowing
the lawn is just gonna be like a little
bit cooler stoned but so like I try to
like watch it when I'm like trying to
get myself too stoned all the time when
I'm just like Oh am I trying to just
make everything a little bit better than
it needs to be or am I like because when
the lawn can be just as fine play my dog
could be just as fine without it yeah I
think it's much like social media where
it's okay if you get that up from it but
can you get the same thing petting your
dog or having fun with your dog without
it if you need weed to have a good time
you need to check yourself if it is
enhancing your time I'm [__] cool
with that right like that is completely
fine I don't know like I kind of have I
don't really know so much what it's like
to not feel hi or what is the word
[__] mind-altering substances my mind
altered I when you met me in eighth
grade I was using meth heroin at 14 15
years old I've had been smoking weed for
a long time I had been drinking for a
long time I've been doing that for a
long time and there is only a very short
periods of my time in my life where I
know what it's like to be me completely
unaltered at all usually those are very
very uncomfortable times in my life and
usually they're also very clear like I
have the most clarity and the most
awe-inspiring epiphanies of my life at
the same time I've gotten a lot of my
motivation and a lot of my sense of
self-worth from when I'm sober when I'm
sober is when I tell myself that I am a
[__] beast and I can do this I tend
to get down not get down on myself but
like ah man you just did you're just a
[__] slacker bla bla bla
yeah go truck some mouthwash type deal
when I'm into mouthwash I need ice
telling you everybody on the internet
thinks I chug mouthwash on a daily basis
he does I do but uh I forgot what I was
saying but I'm the motivation to like
actually
what were we talking about the mouthwash
thing totally [__] threw me off but
yeah [__] just using things in
moderation in like having like a regular
consciousness of sober like yes I don't
have as good to do grasp on it and so
it's hard for me to decide am I using
this weed for a good reason
am i drinking for the right reason I've
gone through times in the past two years
where I have been a stone-cold blackout
drunk alcoholic and now at that point in
my time in life that sounds completely
unattractive to me okay
which part of me is the actual base
level where I'm going to slake where I
operate from am I an alcoholic trying to
be sober or am i a sober person who just
had a weird year you know cuz I don't
I've never had a problem with alcohol
before so like I try to like why was I
doing that what was I getting out of or
why am i smoking weed now and as long as
I feel like it's for I can enjoy life
without it I can do things without it
like I don't have to be drunk or stoned
when I go on stage I don't need to be
drunk or stoned to perform I don't need
to be drunk or stoned to be with my
girlfriend to be with my friends but it
enhances it so I'm cool with it
the moment that I stop hanging out with
my friends cuz I don't got any weed is
the moment that I stop smoking weed
right I feel instantly so that takes
chug a beer yeah right now see I don't I
don't drink I don't really get like
[__] up too often like a couple times
a year like like we have a couple trips
that we do and I'm like yeah I'm get
ready man I'm like taking extra fiber
and I'm like I gotta be drinking this
much more water because next week we're
doing this thing but now I don't know I
feel like the under tractors my thing
for a long time was coke I just [__]
love cocaine there's never never a thing
for me yeah it was a for me you know
what's crazy is I think a lot of it was
I would get together with people in in
in we would just be dreamers man like we
it was a lot of like the one time I gave
myself permission to feel something I
think yeah and and I also so I started
doing a lot more coke I try it before
but I started doing a lot more coke Wow
when I when I got off antidepressants
because I had this [__] I actually
had a reddit comment that like flipped
my something in my [__] brain that
like hurt me and I was on
antidepressants
they went through a bunch of stages if I
hated all of them and they sucked and
they weren't working for me and then I
finally up my dose up my dose and I was
like okay I had a few days or a few
weeks it's like okay I'm feeling pretty
levelled out like I but it it was a
weird feeling and then I was reading
this reddit comment that was like it
basically said like you know inner
presses work for me really really well
and then I suddenly realized that it
wasn't actually me and I was just using
the you know I was just feeling that
because the drug was blocking out so it
was like something that just put it like
bling like bluntly and I was like oh no
and then so I went through a few more
months of like getting off of them and
cold turkey and then it turned into and
this is not all blaming like what I
would do cocaine just because it's
[__] fun like how it was you know but
this kind of led me into this like oh is
that this weird not feeling anything
like because because a lot of times
antidepressants can make you they level
you out but it's it's like you don't
feel the extreme sadness but you also
don't feel the extreme like yeah and I'm
someone who's like I'm just sometimes I
am up and down like some you know ADHD
or whatever like so it was kind of like
giving me something to feel whereas
before I was just not feeling anything
and it was at one time you could
actually start to like talk from me my
true self because I was actually letting
myself feel excitement talking about
dreaming like what I want to do I think
that resonates with a lot of people do I
because I instantly when you said that I
kind of like oh wow so many people that
I have because I'm not a very big
cocaine guy but I have a lot of friends
who have been and I've been in those
rooms you know what I mean so many
people I've talked to I want to be a
singer I actually want to do this is my
actually have a dream of this and then
they never tell you that until your yeah
that room gets lines deep and it's
almost like they needed that to feel
comfortable with themselves because how
dare I ever be a singer how dare I ever
have a dream and it lets you feel that
right it allows you to become the thing
that you are hoping to be without ever
actually having to do the emotional work
to get there right like oh yeah it's so
crazy how excited I feel now just
knowing that like I I don't just talk
about it and I'm really like like
accepting what I want for myself and I'm
like yeah I am work
and I'm more realistic about like the
timeframe of like everything you do
everyday is just a little more [__]
chipping away at it it's actually
interesting to think about just just
like the inability of our sis of our not
society but a lot of us to like dream
out loud without feeling that we can and
without feeling like put down for it or
without trying to explain our way out of
it or without feeling silly like
especially if you're self-aware yeah ooh
okay okay so I heard this thing I heard
this thing so the Martin Luther King I
have a dream speech that apparently and
I just heard this a couple weeks ago he
had a friend or a family member somebody
who was actually behind him and he was
going on and he was he was on the script
and he was saying what he had to say and
I have a dream speech it was actually
off the off the dome I guess wow that
was that was a freestyle of some sorts
right surely somebody behind him was
leaning forward and going tell them
about the dream
well Italy so I want to fact-check this
for sure I wish we had a Jamie but it's
Joey's got I quite imagine if you were
there
what a mess if he wasn't there do what
would we be [__] talking about what
would our world be I think that like in
in that's what I want this podcast to be
to inspire people to do that too is is
like [__] dude if you got a friend who's
telling you about some [__] tell them I
know you more than a lot of people do
bro and like if you really look into it
but like dude I know that you can do
this yeah you gotta [__] just put some
work in be realistic but don't [__]
crush anybody's dreams well you are that
thing the the dice that you have rolled
that of like that you've landed here
because so far you haven't really been
trying you have rolled a lot of people
you have just kind of landed where
you're at
my mom did this my dad did this we lived
here I went to school here I got offered
a job here this is my life secretly I
want to be a singer that place that you
landed is not you that thing that you
are dreaming quite possibly is really
that's the actual you the thing that
you're like telling yourself that you
can't talk about unless you're on
cocaine that quite possibly is your
actual self that's why you're so it's
that Jim Carrey quote
it's your avatar telling you that you're
not in the correct spot you just landed
here you're not guy who works at the
mill that's not you bro
your cousin got you a job that doesn't
define you that's not your [__] goal
in life and you're telling yourself that
you can't be
[__] guitar player or whatever did
when that is so much more true to your
bones than anything else you've ever
done in your life you're just scared
because people landed you in a place or
you landed in a place and that's what it
is that's the thing I've always had a
hard time accepting where I've landed
mm-hmm I cannot land here this is not it
I know I know for a fact that this is
not where I'm supposed to be and I think
people have a hard time stomaching that
from me cuz it can come off as
narcissistic when I'm like this is not
gonna be my career but I know that this
is not it for me and I think that a lot
of people are not realizing that it's
like living someone else's truth or
something yeah like it's it's it's it's
just crazy like to see like how many and
when you are a dreamer or someone who is
on the on the fringes or you're somebody
who's just a creative or like I'm just
like you probably have it too like it
seems like people are more apt to tell
you like panic and I wish that I was
like a stand-up comedian Oh more than
any other art but go ahead yeah right
but it's I don't know I think just just
to put a little plug in that's that
specific thought so a listener I think
just realized when you're when you're on
either sides of these coins like if one
of your friends is kind of just like
casually given a little like oh or maybe
you guys are [__] up and it's 4:00
a.m. and you just did three grams and
your friends like bro I want to be an
actor so bad story today you know what
tomorrow bro let's stop doing cocaine at
10:30 tomorrow bro let's stop doing
cocaine and at some point at some point
next week let's stop but no what you're
saying is correct and I think that goes
with the Jim Carrey quote of you feel
like you are this person but if you
actually what you think is uncomfortable
for you you think that the most
uncomfortable thing in the world would
be to put yourself out there and really
try acting oh my god that sounds
terrible the most uncomfortable thing in
the world is what you're doing your job
that you hate that is the most
uncomfortable thing in the world even if
you failed and you went and tried to be
an actor you would be a lot more
comfortable doing that because you'd be
happy and you would die knowing [__] I
tried and you would have that sense of
like okay I did the thing I did it you
beam
more comfortable being what you truly
want to be at your heart then the job
that you were assigned at birth in your
town you know you think you're more
comfortable you're not you so much more
comfortable in your own water well so we
have a whole we have a whole generation
is such a generalization but like think
about you know our parents like how they
were raised our parents ages they're
raised to like work you know work in
factories and work in jobs and what you
do whatever it's a our way of like
thought is is completely different like
it's I'm just kidding I'm just I'm
always trying to look at like the kids
who are going at now in trainers
yeah our parents right they were taught
but but it's so different like it's so
like it's like here here's exactly what
you do and if you question it they're
like it's because you do it come on it's
it's cuz they're like well why would I
why would I apply at that job if I don't
really want to work they're like cuz you
need a 401k you idiot and you're like
why do I need a 401k because you want to
retire when they don't you and you're
like like this isn't mean like this
reminds me not to like [__] bring up
my own self promote right now but I have
a song called something about working
and the lyrics are something about
working every [__] weekend you say it
is not worth it they say you're
overthinking no I'm not I like that yeah
like you're not overthinking there is
something about [__] working every
weekend and it's killing you right stop
figure out a way to make it to marry the
two because I understand you have to
survive I understand that we have to pay
our bills and everything but you cannot
keep on just talking about this part of
you when you do cocaine you have to let
it all live together it has to all be
free I did not become a full person and
realize Who I am until I started being
comfortable with the fact that I want to
be a stand-up comedian if I only talked
about it when I did cocaine dude I would
have been that a long time ago no I
would have given up a long time ago I
you have to be comfortable with your
dreams you know let yourself have it
yeah let yourself feel like you were
saying earlier it was the only time that
you would let yourself feel em hmm dude
[__] that's heavy like as soon as you
said that I was like yes I think that's
probably resonant for a lot of people
who have cocaine
problems is it is okay I can let it out
now it's never been a thing for me I
don't know if I have a TD or ADHD but I
tend to have the symptoms of it where
uppers are very overwhelming for me and
I've never liked that kind of stuff
I get very anxiety-ridden and I already
have enough anxiety and depression as it
is but I've never been a fan of that
hallucinogens even that type of thing is
a little scary for me I got offered DMT
last night but I was in the world I was
scared I was scared I was in the woods
you would have been in another [__]
dimension you know I like to be on
someone's couch it two-sentence setting
is the psychedelics and I'm just saying
that because I list do it a lot I have
not done psychedelics anything I did LSD
on accident I think that's a way to do
it I had done three triple stacks of
ecstasy we're at a rave in Seattle I was
[__] up beyond belief and I took a
pill from a stranger and then I was
seeing comic book bubbles with the
letter R [__] was crazy it would be hard
to differentiate differentiate into like
what's really going on with you when
you're that deep into a [__] no no I
always happening like I was I was
convincing was it convincing myself that
my friends weren't my friends it was
like weird I would not be not to say
that the person I am today is very great
but I am very proud that I am not the
person that I was going to be and I
think that I am a lot better than I was
and I would not be the person that I am
without hallucinogens without psilocybin
and without dimethyltryptamine I would
not be me you need can you tell me why
when I was about 15 just to give you
some reference to like what kind of kid
I was at the time Jake kind of knew me
back then I was in and out of juvie
every other week every other weekend I
smoked meth I smoked heroin three weeks
before this life-changing psilocybin
trip I got the tattoo
[__] happens on my knuckles when I was
15 years old so that's the kind of kid I
was I had no hopes of a future if you
asked me what I wanted to be I would
have said I just want to skate and be a
functioning drug addict I'll do whatever
I'll sell Joe like that was my goal you
know what I mean I had no sense of I am
a good person whatsoever my buddy
who shall rename nameless but let's call
him Jordan because that's his real name
he sold me these shrooms and he was like
hey listen I grew these in my basement
they're not normal and I'm like Oh
normal only eat one or two and I was
like okay so me being me I the whole bag
which was 1/8 and it was a way too much
and the initial thing happened of I'm
just seeing crazy things right
I would blink my eyes and all of my
friends we were sitting around a
campfire all of my friends would
disappear and then I would blink my eyes
again and they would come back it was
pretty wild
um my friends tried to bring me some
food it looked like it was covered in
maggots the classic stuff my uncle
walked around the corner of the house
and he looked like he was 20 feet tall
and he was like resting his elbow on the
[__] roof just all kinds of things
like that
my cousin looked like he was covered in
scales and had a tail whatever my
girlfriend's this is my favorite one
though I have to say this one
my girlfriend's nose the end of her nose
started blowing up like a helium balloon
oh and then it popped in my face and the
flesh man all over me whoa so at this
point wait did that flip it traumatizing
all sudden like that's not fun at all
none of this for some reason Rob really
tall uncle it was so funny because it's
right it was extremely unsettling and
frightening my chain my figure Oh 2006
gangster chain turned into a snake
crawled down my pants so I thought
everyone was trying to kill me I needed
my mom or my brother to come and pick me
up this is very common when you trip out
the only people you trust is your mother
that's the only person who wasn't trying
to kill me I have my brother come and
pick me up
of course he messes with me the whole
entire ride home convincing me that I'm
in a spaceship whatever you know I get
home and my mom as soon as I get home I
enter this realm of safety mm everything
becomes less dark it becomes okay
I literally I'm 16 15 years old I have
my mom cradle me in her arms like a baby
and I make her put her hand in my mouth
and people can't see this but I make her
put her hand with her fingers in my
mouth and her palm on the bottom of my
chin kind of like you would facemask
somebody in football perfect [__]
description
I did that because if you've ever seen
The Grudge when people's jaws fall off
it felt like my jaw was doing that and I
needed her reassurance that it wasn't
happening so I sound fun it no it was
traumatizing and to this day I have
nightmares about it it was not fun but I
closed my eyes and then I went into this
nowhere place I didn't have a body but
what is the body huh what is me I don't
even know what the concept of where's
the edges yes I was just a floating ball
of gas and I was in this black realm and
then my probation officer at the time
shows up from the abyss and starts
walking towards me I didn't know that's
who it was she opens up a case folder
and starts reading me basically
someone's like life stats
you know I mean like what happened in
their life she was telling me about
myself but I had full amnesia I did not
know who I was
whatsoever I was just like why are you
telling me this and then she was like
this is you and it all hit me at once
instantly every memory I ever had of all
my whole life and I'm not a good kid I'm
on heroin meth all this [__] my reality
hits me how it would hit a stranger you
know what I mean right
I am seeing myself from someone else's
perspective and it [__] me up and my
mom was going through this with me like
I'm asking my mom like this is really me
I'm remembering things like this is who
I am I go to juvie all the time I smoked
heroin like this is really me mom and
she's like yes son this is this is
really you and I'm like [__] I don't
like this I'm gonna change and I didn't
fully change I've still had battles with
drug addiction since then I've still had
bottle battles with the look I will say
this I didn't have a run-in with the law
or do anything criminal for ten years
until I got a DUI after that I
completely changed my life like I
completely changed the way I was as like
a like the stealing and robbing and
lying and terrible kid breaking into
people's houses I robbed every
elementary school in store in this town
whoop statute of limitations anyways it
was more than 10 years ago kids I
already checked so I was just this
terrible person and I stopped doing that
I stopped being that I still had my
faults I still was a cheater I still
wasn't the best husband I wasn't the
best boyfriend I wasn't the best son but
I
changed a lot about me and I would not
have done that without psilocybin
mushrooms it showed me to myself I got
to meet me man
do you think it like Mike it pulled the
real you out from in there
like it's like Oh like you didn't even
know it was in how we were saying like
that's not the real actual you like yes
it showed me to like because the person
was saying oh that wasn't actually me it
was the drugs I was underneath all of
that yes it made me realize ik no you're
not a piece of [__] dude you're not some
punk rock spit on someone's face and you
didn't want love yes I wanted that blood
I wanted to be cool when I was a kid
really bad well I'm just saying like
like the essence of everyone's being in
this whole world like what the one thing
like what are you kind of leaning
towards more than anything love yes yes
that is the goal yeah that is what we
all want is to be loved and to love that
showed me a lot of things and I still
had a really rough go from there like I
still had a rough go at being a father I
still had a rough go at drug addiction I
never was addicted to heroin as a
teenager but later on around 20 19 years
old I picked it up randomly get this
because it made my voice sounded cool
and when I would record started is I
liked the way it made my voice sound now
the way it turned into a real addiction
but even then I kind of managed it and
maintained it to where it was never
anything public it was never anything
that like was like holy [__] Joseph go
to rehab but it was always a problem but
um I wasn't perfect after that
psilocybin trip is what I'm saying
but the DMT trip that I had that did a
whole nother Mindwipe and changed a
bunch of perspectives on me too that is
a whole different ballgame I recommend
if you feel like you have the mental
capacity to handle it and you can be in
a safe environment and you can do it in
a controlled environment even if you can
go to a therapist in a state where it's
legal
I recommend hallucinogenic therapy
psychedelic therapy it's really good DMT
really helped me to I I study a lot of
this [__] and I kind of like I have my
projections for where I think the future
is gonna be with it and I think that
psilocybin especially but like a lot of
these hulusi genetics are going to like
weird sick
see five-year-old Debbie is taking
[__] psilocybin in three years for
sure like so there they have so much
[__] success rate with people and
depression and anxiety in PTSD and all
this [__] and I'm so excited for a
little bit so yeah dude I thanks for
sharing your [__] story that's so
awesome that you shared that it was
advanced change would you like to share
your DMT one as well that one's good
that's not so long that was a quick one
I can okay so that one was a whole
different so the first one was
psilocybin and they all react
differently to you and you react
differently to them the best way I ever
heard someone put it is acid is like
you're the driver and psilocybin is like
you're the passenger DMT is like what
the [__] is a car on a rocket yeah so I
did DMT I was with my ex at the time
this was before any of our really toxic
things have happened and everything was
honeymoon and great vibes you know I
mean I'm in a hotel room with a lovely
shag carpet it was great perfect setting
you know I mean I never seen a hotel
room with a loveseat that was great
or no not a loveseat but like a full it
was like a house it was lovely
so it got presented to me I didn't plan
on doing it just kind of popped up we
were offered it we go to this hotel room
we do it I kind of did this weird thing
where I broke through but I did
something which is really rare breaking
through is you could trip out on DMT or
you could break through which is like a
life-changing experience like you blast
off into the cosmos and you know when
you broke through because it's like you
come out of it crying and [__] um you
could either have a little trip or you
could break through I did this weird
middle plane thing where I still had
function over my body and I could walk
around and control myself but I was not
[__] here tell you that much
it basically did this for me I felt
everything bad that anybody had ever
done to me in my life all at one [__]
moment like every single wrong that had
ever happened to me that I perceive is
the wrong that the my stepdad beating me
the my father abandoned me like just
random things you know what I mean any
wrong I ever perceived in life was
thrown on me all at once and it was in
the metaphor of mud dolloping on me and
like
taking me down til I was like in a fetal
position and when it was all along and I
felt like I was gonna suffocate at this
one moment this light appeared in my
mind and it told me to just let it all
go and I forgave every and I mean this
I'm not just saying this is like oh oh
stupid new and this is why I don't like
to talk about DMT because it makes you
seem very like hippie-ish I'm very
skeptical and not a very spiritual
person guys like this is very evident to
me what happened to me everything that I
ever felt in my life that happened to me
I forgave people everybody everybody
whoever did anything I forgave that's
the [__] power of that and the mud
fleN off of me in like this weird
explosion and I like it was like those
memes where you see the chick like fling
her hair out of the water all sexy or
Jason Momoa I did that and the mud flew
off of me and then I felt every bad
thing I had ever done to somebody else
ooh yeah that was way worse yeah way
[__] worse all the things I had done
to somebody who how God our psyches are
so [__] like how could you possibly
just pull all of that like alright
here's everything I've been taking
Italia the back of my mind and all of
it's right here and I just tip the
bucket over so how does our psyche
understand that it was like walking
through a long corridor with a thousand
to a million doors on each side and each
door you look in there's you having a
conversation with yourself and you know
each conversation as they're going on
you know exactly what was being said it
was insane but then in the sense in the
same instant that I felt all the wrongs
I did I forgave myself and one thing
that rang true in my head was we are not
our fault we are not defined defined by
our faults the bad things you've done
are bad you shouldn't have done them but
that's not you and that goes at this
whole cancer culture [__] that's why I
don't feel it like other people feel
that I don't feel the need to take this
man's livelihood away or this woman's
you're not defined by that I'm sorry
you're not the bad things you did in
life absolutely I mean there's
exceptions like if you're [__] Ted
Bundy you're kind of your faults okay
for the most part for us everyday people
man don't define yourself by the bad
things you did that's something I
struggle with every day to this day is I
am the bad things I've done but I'm not
I'm not [__] they're just bad things
that I've done yeah they're not they're
just they're just they're just things in
my
that are like hey you need to learn
about this more than you the more than
you know yeah thank you look in we're a
trip over some [__] sometimes you know
what did you do that brought you to that
point it can't all just be my nurture it
can't all just be what happened to me
what is your nature what part did you
play in this I once got cheated on and
I'm not even playing
I really really and I know it's not my
fault she shouldn't have cheated I mean
that's okay I get it guys I really
evaluated what I was doing to cause
myself to get cheated on mmm I didn't
have my own place at the time I was kind
of a loser I was sleeping on a couch or
in my car I didn't have any motivation
you know what I mean I wasn't like being
everything I could like out you know and
I evaluated like how could I have
prevented this you know what I mean I
still shouldn't have got cheated on and
I hope you [__] know it you broke my
heart but I did way out what did I do to
make myself uh cheat honorable right you
know yeah you got to bring that
awareness there's two sides to every
story I was being a lame I was so poor
but yeah there is I want to I want to
swing back to your band I don't want to
miss that just because that's Newhall
yeah so so I didn't know you as and we
to skate together back in the day not
that I like [__] super knowing now at
all either but nobody really does tell
me about do you write the music like
because I'm asking as someone who is I'm
a new musician I've been a DJ for a
while but I'm not a musician I I'm well
I'm new I'm not I'm getting less afraid
to show people the world my [__] but it
still sucks I hope it's good to fifteen
years but so I'm just really curious
about bands and writing I think we are
very much so in the same either mind
whether we whether it's true or not were
very much so in the same state of mind
in the same realm right now we're on the
way over here I was like Jake is my DJ
friend he knows about music not me like
so you know what I mean like even I am
in that realm of like I [__] all's I
know is how to hit notes that's all I
got baby I got pipes that's it yeah and
I actually wanted to create a we're
gonna be doing a lot of things on our
YouTube channel
it's an interview series based around
the fact that I don't know [__] about
music and all my friends do yeah yes my
friends are super knowledgeable and I
want to ask them about it you know I
don't write music per se my friend does
all the guitar he comes to me with ideas
or I come to him with ideas
Scotty biscone or my [__] guitar
seems amazingly talented he's one of the
more talented musicians in terms of
guitar I would say in the Pacific
Northwest and he's in a really great
band called outlet they're signed to ten
city records he's the lead singer of
that check that band out um outlet and
he does all of the guitar picky stuff
every once in a while I'll bust out a
[__] harmonica or a tambourine or
something you know and I'm pretty sure I
have a harmonic on me right now I always
keep one on me I keep that bang on me to
go yeah I guarantee you I do but um we
write it really cohesively and almost
jam band like where he comes to me with
something and I will just start singing
and it didn't Evatt ibly becomes a song
but um right now we're about four songs
deep into our first album EP we don't
really know what it's gonna be our band
is called stay in prison our first
project is gonna be called is called
four loko green-apple strong cider honey
is it four loko [__] it's a grocery list
that my friend had one day and it's I
love it I didn't know I was a musician I
kind of sung in private when I was a kid
and I did a lot of impersonations
singing like if a song came on the radio
I was really good at sounding just like
that guy whether it be Phil Collins or
all my voice like that yeah I love doing
like God was in Garth Brooks so that
whatever and then lo play yes I was
great at doing that and also changing
the lyrics I've never sung a song
correctly in my [__] life she she
will vouch for it I just letting it my
girlfriend obsessed Haley's gonna be
laughing so hard when she hears this
because I'm not was what I love to make
her I just love to make her laugh by
changing the lyrics I am the weird I
love my life so I I never really took it
seriously though much like stand-up
comedy when I was a kid I was just like
oh that's something that I kind of do
that's cute but I'm not like passionate
about being a singer
around like four or five years ago my
cousin died I was trying to figure out
what I wanted to do with my life
inspired me to pull myself out of that I
am NOT my job at the chicken factory
saying you know and I was trying to
figure out what I wanted to do
journalism singing comedy and I started
teaching myself how to sing mostly by
just being in my car and being very very
loud and obnoxious and every day I would
get a little bit better and a little bit
better and then people started to hear
me singing because I had friends who are
musicians and then people are starting
to ask me to be in their band and then
people are starting to ask me to be in
their projects and that's how I met Jake
the bass player for Rose tan we were in
a little project called Ross Avenue
[__] about a year and a half two
years ago I Jake is the [__] one of my
favorite musicians in town he's a good
dude love that guy me and him
jammed very well together and I love row
Stan but then eventually it much like we
were saying where it becomes evident
like I put something out and people go
hey that's good I sing in people like
hey sing in my band and I'm like okay I
did it I wheeled myself into the I made
people think that I am a musician I'm
not I just taught myself how to sing two
years ago so I'm learning as I go
it's a learning process every day I'm
learning how to record I'm learning how
to structure music luckily my friends
are [__] geniuses I have a lot of
support and help in that realm I knows a
lot of the I'm in the scene luckily I
weaseled my way into it whereas if I was
just in my living room or in my bedroom
making YouTube videos doing my own thing
and not putting myself out there not
going out there and oh you play guitar
play let me sing or just a meeting
people and put yourself out there in the
art that you want to be in and
eventually that bobber is gonna dunk
under and someone's gonna ask you to do
something or you're gonna get to do it
if you that's great don't not make
videos at home keep doing that but
definitely try to put yourself out there
in the scene because if I didn't do that
I wouldn't be in a band right now and I
think don't wait till you think you're
good to like like don't don't wait till
you like because me like I'm I sing
a little good comedy I don't care if you
suck ass get out there and do open mics
dude right right open mics are a super
super important thing we're talking
about that we'll just flip the script on
that so open mics I think a lot of times
when we go out we go out to see let's
say we're just someone who doesn't do
any creative we're never up on the stage
we're just someone who consumes we're
someone who just goes out to bars
without - comedy clubs once in a while I
would see comedians mm-hmm as an
audience member we have a job right yeah
like I I think that you know and we can
we can dive into hecklers - like I'd
love to talk about the ridiculousness of
Henry I don't think people realize they
have a job and they often time get their
job confused right bro okay so let's
dive in that I think I feel very
strongly about this and I'm looking
forward to hearing your opinion because
as a DJ you deal with a different kind
of it's a different kind you deal with
drawn girl coming up with a dollar bill
telling you to play uh sure yeah yes
[__] it's hilarious but I but you do
it's super true I think that people
don't see it as a suicide relationship
they don't understand like the same as
like a girl coming up to me with a song
request saying I want to hear the song
okay well if I just took if I took
everybody's favorite song in this room
there's 150 people if I took 150 songs
everybody's favorite song and I [__]
mash them together it'd be garbage it'd
be [__] trash your opinion sucks yeah
let me work I know what I'm doing dude
literally it's like like you're trying
out society you're like where's society
at how come and push against it I'm like
reading this room I'm looking at what
you're wearing from head to toe the
second you walk in the door and seeing
what your vibe might be like it's been
my goal for the past month to make sure
that this is good don't you get that
you've just been thinking about it for
the last three minutes I've been I've
been working 24/7 everywhere I'm DJing
I'm every time I get in my car I'm
looking at what's hot I'm looking at the
new songs I'm like liking I'm putting
into this place and put it in that place
I'm more into lyrics I'm I'm literally
making mashups in my head as I'm driving
to the gym for my gig next [__] 18th
of the month
like in your doing the same thing your
life is being worked at all times I
actually was hoping that we would get to
something along these lines of
conversation because I have a big love
hate relationship with crowds man it's
because I've done a lot of local shows
bar shows comedy shows I performed in
every aspect you can think of I've
hosted concerts you've DJ the DJ the
concerts I've hosted I've seen all
different kinds of shows and all
different kinds of people so there's
different kinds of audience members and
there's different kinds of people and
there's different kinds of venues I
could say for a fact that you do have a
job as an audience member and it is not
to be a part of the show in any more of
a factor than to laugh if I ask you a
question answer me if I ask the crowd a
question and to me trust me
the thing that you just thought of is
not as good as the punchline that I've
been thinking up for the past three
years in practicing and you're throwing
me off and now I have to make the whole
thing and now I sound like a dick I know
but you guys I love you and I want you
to keep coming but let me work just know
this thing okay and there's a big
difference between performing in a bar
and performing in a comedy club
I call it combat comedy when you perform
in a bar when you perform in a bar it's
uh make me laugh when you perform at a
comedy club it's make me laugh yeah I'm
it ready to laugh yes I am here to laugh
let's do this people in bars tend to
think that their job and what comedy is
is my ability to react to them that is
not what being a stand-up comedian is
that's what being a person is my ability
to react to what you're saying that is
not what's going on here you are not on
the flyer you're not on the bill it's
not Joseph and audience it is Joseph
Crum just let me do my thing guys I will
talk to you guys I'll come out in the
crowd trust me but just let things
happen the way they're gonna happen you
have no idea how nerve-racking it is
when you're about to say something and
somebody else says something and you
have to switch and then go back to that
thing and then the thing loses its power
dude you can timing is everything that's
like a typical saying but literally you
could miss the beat and fall off the
joke yeah and a lot of people I don't
think they realize when they're seeing
me perform is a lot different when
they're seeing other stand-up comedians
perform because I lost my ability to
drive because I fell asleep in a talk
about drive through very drunk one night
don't do it and it makes it very hard to
get to open mics and perform like I used
to to get that open mics perform like I
used to 2016 I was at every single one
but I can't do that now so a lot of
times the only time I perform all year
is when I get booked for a gig I am very
thankful for the fact that I am a four
year comedian and I get booked for gigs
that's unheard of that's you don't get
booked for gigs - you're ten years in
usually so I'm very lucky in that sense
but that means that most comedians when
you see their half-hour or their 15
minutes or their hour they have been
doing it every night repeatedly over and
over and over again
I prefer perform once a month once every
two months - the same crowd which means
I have to write a new thing every month
half hour long and it has I can't say
the same thing because you guys were
there last month and I don't get to
practice it at all and when you talk
that's scary man yeah and now I hope you
guys like think about my performances
where they haven't like gone so great at
blue sky or whatever and frame it in
that sense that that half hour speech I
told that was the first time I ever told
it I didn't get to practice it I didn't
get to go to open mics I didn't get to I
am different than other comedians I
don't get that privilege dude I think
that being a small town comedian or
being a small like I always say it with
DJs - like if you can impress a crowd as
a DJ in a small town yeah of people who
don't realize that they're even
opinionated I'm not there being let's
get a [__] dude is it's good you learn
the diverse things and you also are
forced to just you can't just beat the
same horse it's like even if a joke
killed for me like I would make I was
looking back at my Mixcloud the other
day I was like updating my am like names
on there cuz like kind of fading out the
Khronos name and I was like [__]
looking back at my old catalog for my
2015 2014 and I was like I got like you
know 50 mixes on here whatever and like
they're each an hour long is I Beach
like so much [__] time that I put in
because a lot of them were shows a lot
of them were like specific nice to the
club like I all
tried to treat the night as it's as a
one special moment in time like in when
you listen to the mix you can kind of go
back to that and I feel like as a
comedian running in a small town when
you're really trying to write like like
what's going on right now and where am i
but you have to abandon those mixes huh
yeah that's it once I once I release
them especially online I don't even like
to use the same transitions between two
songs anymore earlier we were talking
over the phone about Andrew Andrew
Schultz and how he's kind of changed the
way people are viewing comedy in the
sense of less is more like I can't tell
you if you come to see me and you've
already seen my hour online you're not
gonna laugh you're gonna actually be
very mad at me it's not like music
we're play the hits there's only been
one or two comedians who have ever been
able to do that in the history of
mankind that's Andrew Dice Clay and Sam
Kinison I think maybe we can't do that
so usually you're not gonna see a lot of
output from stand-up comedians and once
I let something out to you guys if I put
something on Facebook if I put something
on Instagram I don't that's it that's it
yeah I don't get the joke that's it I
don't get to replay it I don't get to
tell it again yeah I don't get to use it
onstage you're gonna be really mad at me
if I start reciting my facebook post on
stage you paid 10 20 bucks to see me
you're gonna very upset and I'm not
trying to fight so but yeah and I think
that's the mix is the very same thing
and I can't get married two things but I
also have to protect certain aspects
like there's bits that I have that I
love that people are never gonna see
until you come and see me you're never
gonna see on Facebook you're never gonna
see on an Instagram I will not give this
up until it's on my first hour special
but Andrew Schultz he comes in and says
okay that's great I'm gonna film every
set I have and every bit that I can give
away every one that I can give up for
adoption everyone that I can abort
everyone crowd piece of crowd work that
I'm not married to and you know a piece
of crowd work can turn into a bit he
could have took that three-minute clip
and took that piece of crowd work and
fleshed it out and materialized it and
saved it for his hour special and then
people would have watched the first 20
minutes of it on Netflix and then they
would have clicked off and he's a white
male and he wouldn't got that much
traction what he did instead was all
these three minute for minute five
minute
in flooded Instagram and Facebook and
changed the way Facebook comedians and
stand-up comedians and online comedian
just how you operate changed it
completely I need to start doing that as
well I'm not gonna be able to do that
until I start regularly doing open mics
though right I got to get out there and
do open mics I have footage of me on
stage but I said I don't put it out
because I [__] likes those jokes and
I want to keep telling them but we are
in a new age with social media a tik-tok
age of vine age whatever you want to
call it where that hour-long special a
year that is not conducive to how the
[__] internet works anymore mhm that
it next no yeah that's not gonna work
but I want more every day all the time
okay luckily to you [__] I'm
funny 24/7 but hold on let me figure out
how I'm gonna put this out like it I
can't just throw it out there I have to
put it and present it in a pretty way
people even take it serious so like
Andrew Schultz was doing a lot of it cuz
wasn't he on with like Charlemagne
didn't they have a then they have a
podcast together brilliant idiot so I
was just listening to it yesterday it's
good [__] yeah I mean I think that he
was smart and it's kind of look at what
Joe Joe Rogan's do it does his comedian
like what he started doing is like where
do you get good content is from [__]
regular conversation yeah you just you
get out there and you just keep doing
stuff it sounds like you've been doing a
lot of [__] - just trying to like keep
working keep the momentum going trying
to pull it out yeah that's totally
derailed everything I had going but I'm
putting out an hour-long special a year
at this point is like putting out a 15
minute podcast and expecting to get
something out of it mm-hmm you know what
I mean like you're gonna need more I
need to work way harder I need more and
it's like okay I'll give it but okay so
how does okay so we were talking about
audience and then we're talking about
just kind of the different comedy in a
live setting and comedy on social media
what's our audience on social media like
do they have a job is there because like
you can't just let it turn into a
[__] cesspool of comments - I think
there's also an audience on the other
end of I'm in the midst of trying to
figure out how to monetize this and make
it a thing now it's I don't think I've
ever actually said this on recording and
I hope nobody
from any other art takes us in a bad way
it's not anything I'm saying about about
this art it's just kind of the way
comedy gets treated my jokes don't get
treated the same way my photography fee
front my photography friends photos get
treated my jokes don't get treated the
same way my friends song gets treated
you know what I mean
there's a different realm of support for
jokes and for comedy than there is for
other things and you kind of have to do
it on your own yeah it's way it's with
it's it's a do I personally feel this
specific content or not not oh this is a
great joke from my friend who I want to
support in this way yeah exactly like my
friends don't share my stuff because
they're being supportive of me they only
share my stuff when I really make them
laugh yeah it's so if it has nothing to
do with them personally the joke its I
even have to win over my [__] friends
but luckily my friends love me and
they're great they share my [__] all the
time so that's wonderful but there's
just a different way that the audience
when it comes to stand-up comedy in
person and on the internet there are way
different things the way your friends
react I don't expect anything for my
friends or family I know that that's not
the way anybody become successful you
need a good support system yes you need
people to believe in you that helps you
also need people to not believe in you
but you have to just let your content go
onto the internet and speak for itself I
think when it comes support is always a
[__] weird word to me I always felt
weird about people supporting me just
because they know me yeah I like I would
always say like like people like would
repost my stuff and say come support
Jake because he's local and I'm like
what if you don't like the music yeah
don't [__] come out man I don't want
to take your time and if you don't like
this [__] what if it's bad I want to say
here's what I'm doing and if there's a
thing that you're into like come enjoy
it and let's have a wonderful time
together like it and I feel like it's
like you you almost have to do that like
well it's like hey do we need to do
cocaine a self-promote on the internet
yes like we were saying earlier like the
people who need to have it to feel
something to like let their dreams out
do I need to do a line to post something
saying hey I'm a face I'm a stand-up
comedian will you come to my show
because that is my biggest downfall I'm
very bad at branding myself and putting
myself
there and going hey guys will you
support this will you share this will
you come to my show well it's dude it's
the same thing it's like it's almost
like believing in yourself out loud like
you almost feels like like you get look
at like rust you know the rapper rest
yeah like at me you introduced me to
rust four years ago holy [__] I said you
I was working out at the gym and I was
like send me some music and you sent me
Russ oh man [__] at eleven right next to
you this [__] it I'll do it myself on
the wall I know I saw ya but a but so
him like so there's not really a world
that exists like in our society if you
believe in yourself you can't really say
it no I can't really like be about that
but not has to say it yeah it's a in its
it's a it's almost like what like what
have you really in your [__] heart
like you think you're neo
like you're like dude I'm literally like
I think like you can't say that out loud
because people are like you know it's a
weird barrier that exists I'll make
myself super uncomfortable right now
here's something I never say out loud
and I just said to her yesterday this is
very narcissistic I think I have
obtained a certain level of comedic
genius I know that sounds crazy guys but
that's what we're talking about is
people are scared to say these things
about themselves Jimmy they're afraid it
shouldn't be [__] it
just say it what is it gonna hurt people
are gonna think I'm crazy good talk
about me talk about how crazy I am make
people go look me up yeah
what about me get my name out there
what if somebody walks up to me in the
treatments a man I think you're crazy
you be like oh wow that's crazy and you
can walk away like like that your life
is not meant by other people's [__]
reactions to what you say or their
opinions of it but then again it's not
like it's an amalgamation of what your
definition of yourself is what you
actually are and what exists in the
Ethio in the ethos that is not to be
judged or predetermined by anybody just
like what your state is like if a
non-biased like entity came here like
what would they think of you there's
what people think of you what you think
of you and then what the gods would
think of you where does it all exist I
don't know hey have you ever tried DMT -
not my nose here I'm breaking the third
wall
third wallet it's the fourth wall
actually the fourth wall yes just Joe
when's the last time you changed your
mind about something dude
all the [__] time all the time I
think that that is one of my biggest
strengths it's such a strength isn't it
yes I am and she probably thinks I'm
crazy for then when I say she guys are
referring to my girlfriend that's
sitting behind me she probably thinks
I'm crazy for this because I will get
mad about something or we'll argue about
something in within three seconds I'm
like hey I'm sorry you were right you
were right and she'll think I'm [__]
with her I'm not [__] with you I
really think I was wrong look I changed
my mind
yeah and the ability to change her mind
the ability to say I don't know the
ability to say I was wrong is one of the
things that is like so punished these
days but also super valuable as a human
being when I see that in somebody I
value that so much but I also understand
that it's super dangerous to do that in
today's day and age people will your
whole entire word can be thrown away if
you don't believe the same [__] that you
believed when you were 13 okay like hey
you tweeted that Digimon is better than
Pokemon you're 13 yeah it's a lake I
don't think that way anymore guys like
that's better
I think did you month better but no it's
it's the same thing like I changed my
mind all the time and probably the last
thing I really like had a heavy heavy
like well [__] there's the coronavirus
thing every other week every other day
I'm sure that it's I need my mask I need
my gloves I need to be as safe as I
possibly can
we need to be patriotic and do the
heroic thing and stay inside and then
the next day I was completely wrong you
know but that's more of a day-to-day
thing that everyone is kind of changing
their mind on if I really had to
pinpoint something that I'd changed my
mind on where I think that this is wrong
I got it boom just popped up in my
facebook memories today two and a half
years ago three years ago and maybe you
remember this this is when I first got
on Facebook and social media
three two and a half years ago I
promised myself to never argue online
again and I did it oh [__] I've not
gotten gotten in an argument on social
media and when I say argument I mean I
don't even bother
I don't even if I disagree with you I'll
state my one thing I'll let you say your
thing I'll say you know what I see so
many ways in which you're right I love
you goodbye
and everybody is always usually like
what the [__] okay sure
or I'll compliment someone's hair sure
sorry she knows this like I'll just
randomly if I feel like an argument is
about to happen
I'll be like dude your hair is so dope
people will be super thrown off by it
but I just don't want to argue three
years ago that's the big thing I changed
my mind on because it was draining me as
a person it was making me feel bad it
was making me angry my significant other
at the times tapped on my shoulder one
day while I was in the middle of a
heated Facebook argument and I stretched
like I snapped around and like what and
in that moment I realized like oh my god
this dude from Colorado arguing with me
about whatever is affecting my mood to
where I just snapped at my girlfriend
right like even though it wasn't I
wasn't matter she tapped my shoulder and
I got kind of alarmed you know but still
like still and 2018 New Year's Day I
promised myself to never do that again
and that it's pointless I'm not changing
anybody's mind the best thing I can do
is find ways that those people relate to
me and then let them find their way to
my beliefs on their own if they want to
it's not my job to make anyone think
anything I used to really think that
part of my purpose on this earth and
that's where I say I guess this is where
I changed my mind I used to want to be a
journalist like really really bad after
my cousin got killed in the jail by the
corrections officers I was super social
justice warrior and everything it
changed my life and I'm not sjw but I
was very just like this is how yes you
know activists and um share where were
wanting to be a journalist okay so what
were we speaking of changing my mind yes
I used to think it was my job to change
people's mind to like I see things that
yes people don't see no like I I am I am
just and I am righteous and you guys are
wrong and if I
I am good at speaking I always have been
and if I can in any way articulate my
point of view in some way that can lead
someone to the light as I saw it then
that is my purpose I really thought that
no that's not my job
my job is to relate to people my job is
to get people to relate to me and my job
is to understand people and get them to
understand me it's not to change their
mind like see see you know it's
interesting as you were says you were
telling me that you have that position I
had a very very similar position but
mine was always like okay I can be the
one who solves the problem for everyone
maybe like people are arguing the
comments okay I see your sign I see your
side and I'm sitting there I'll take an
hour with a Facebook comment sometimes I
or I not anymore I used to a few years
ago and I would be like I guess I you
know I do see Janet's side but also
Debbie you're being a total [__] and
in Clint I you know Clint I know his
background so I know why he's being like
this yeah like it's like I've tried to
solve these problems and I try to get
like one hard-hitting comment that's way
too long to read and I'll give 38 likes
[__] and that would like
reassure me but it'd be [__] we love
it but then it's like what was that
really solving an argument like were
these people really having like a
logical argument in the first place and
you're spreading yourself so thin I
understand and and I see what you're
saying Debbie but also Jim said that
you're spreading yourself so thin
because that was my thing was I felt
like I was the only logical person are
you guys not all seeing this from every
perspective at all times I do that same
[__] yeah I think that we're very
similar in that sense in a major way um
well I'm more logical about that whole
situation yeah okay sure I feel like I
am sometimes the only person who's
seeing it from all perspectives but at
the same time I feel like you could all
easily see it if I just word it the
right way and then you're gonna go ding
and be like okay we all are kind of
right but know what a trap everyone
thinks they're so right just like I do I
think I am so right in the sense that
we're all right when probably one of us
is actually more right but it doesn't
[__] matter
is my point we should just be relating
to each other and just finding finding
what we do then we can start to adore
each other once we relate to each other
then we can admire each other once we
admire each other
we can start to copy each other okay I
[__] like Jake he's funny
also he does this thing really healthy
over there all your [__] that's setup
I'm doing that when I get home bro your
your schedule on your wall oh yeah yeah
I saw I had been following the last
couple months I'm thrown for a loop but
I'd love to talk you through it I like I
like ADHD coronary thing cuz I've
mastered it but I relate to you then I
admire you then I copy your actions you
can't just be like hey guys you should
think this and then expect people to be
like oh ding duh right he's right Wow
okay so I actually had a you just help
me explain kind of like you bro always
trying to figure out ourselves like why
am I the way I am so I'm always like I'm
a super chameleon personality I'm like
what like how because that like
naturally it's like how can I fit into
this and I think it's for me
youngest I have three older sisters and
I was probably on a bunch of people and
I'm probably how do I just like fit in
with whoever I'm with right here that's
probably where is born of but so
chameleon personality when I'm always
trying to like I'm just trying to find
where we level with each other like
we're like so you like next time that we
hang out you know all this information
that we just shared amongst these three
or you know four hours whatever that's
static lovely where we can all operate
yeah and so you have you start having
that with like individual people like
and it's almost like different sides of
your personality it's like I don't know
I just think that I want to advocate for
being a chameleon kind of yeah like just
like it's not you know watch when you're
not being true to yourself and don't
laugh it don't laugh at things and just
agree to things and say yes when you
don't want to say yes but I don't want
you what you connect with if I had to
guess I would say that's more of a
natural state to be in is I am NOT one
thing and I am constantly changing which
eat with each person I am around when
you step into a situation around new
people in different situations and you
don't try to find that level ground you
don't try to find that static level and
you just go this is what I think that's
how you start wars that's how you
fistfight people that's how you ruin a
party that's how you have awkward
meetings find that level that's the
natural state that people are supposed
to be and I think we're we are
constantly changing with each person
we're around because just like there's
that thing we're like a cell changes
every time you like you
serve it like any time you observe
something yeah every time we're around
somebody we become a different cell you
become a different version of you and I
think that's okay like that's important
you should be getting aspects of each of
that pulling it all in to make like one
okay I've pulled in from all these
different realms of thing and then I've
reached this realm of like absolution
this is cool I've reached from the
people I know over here the people I
know over here and I didn't step into
those situations going I'm this and I'm
gonna leave as this right right right I
think it's a it's a good practice of
being those people in those situations
and then for me I know that something
that was really good for my mental
health because I would get too caught up
and being what everybody else needs that
being everybody is everything and like
that little peep documentary I was I
didn't want to call you out but I was
trying to take that like it's to be from
the dog but no but like like trying to
be that without kind of like resurfacing
back at home without like like coming
back into your own brain when you're
like for me like the you know the
introverted like just recharging
function of like huh yeah be everybody's
everything but come back and like make
sure you kind of focus and center
yourself so like you like my it might be
you know if like Tony Robbins like
manifestation sort of thing you don't
have to like do your mantras but like
when you get back home maybe you have
some sort of like I'm a comedian and I
Know Who I am and I want to be this kind
of person to these kind of people I know
I jumped a big gap here yeah but I I'm
wanting more and more every day to just
be a human and a person and not a
comedian you okay like um I'm finding
myself bummed out that I don't have
normal social media I don't have a
social media where I can post my food
and go dinner date with my girlfriend
today or had a hard day I don't get to
do that if you don't have something
funny to say don't say anything at all
that's what my social media is and I I
wish so badly sometimes to just be a
person really just not have to define
myself by what is over here on social
media what is in my mind of Who I am in
terms of an artists
to a creator I just wish I could be
plain-jane sometimes and just be normal
and what is normal right I know that but
be able to say what you want without any
sort of yeah thirdly to just have what
everybody else has where I don't have
that expectation to be funny because I'm
not a stand-up comedian I can just say
things I get introduced by people as a
stand-up comedian sometimes and
instantly I'm like oh now I don't get to
be normal like you know like [__] I
don't get to just sit here and be quiet
no um I find myself more and more every
day wishing that and I could make it I
could go and do it but I don't think
that I would get the same validation
that I get or the same thing or I don't
even think I would like it maybe maybe
I'd be like this is [__] boring and I
inevitably would end up posting
something hilarious anyways right I
don't think that I can be here's my dog
and check out my [__] lawnmower I
don't think I can be that guy I don't
know but I want to be let me [__]
dope maybe one day maybe that'll be the
new retirement maybe it'll be like in
the future like now that you're over
this age and you've done these things in
your life we're gonna give you your in
on the private your on the private
social media accounts you get on this
and everybody is over the age of 65 I
don't have to be anything other than
themselves Miami knows that people naked
nudes here whatever the [__] we want
thank you yeah I don't um I actually
I've never taken a nude in the sense
yeah of lake this is if you saw that
picture you'd be like that's Joseph
naked have you like a full-body nude
have you ever done that yeah for sure
and have a lot of tattoos that would
just be like yeah they're probably in my
phone but they're probably less about
the nude you gotta ask me and I don't
have any saved so I have to go to my
bathroom now at my aunt's house dude I
was thinking about this I mean is she
what if she has the only full-body
mirror exactly I'm not at her house I
drove over there she just has a really
good mirror oh you like it I just needs
bad
but no I don't know I'm I'm I've never
done anything like sorry to take it to
that place
I was just wondering I'm weird about
nudes and I'm really bad at flirting on
social media uh I don't do it even when
I'm single and everything like that I'm
very bad at it dolly this is how she got
me she just sent me a fire emoji okay
and then we met each other we met each
other two days later that's all you need
that's all if she would have said
anything more I would've been okay too
much now I got elaborate on my thoughts
and think yeah not good at it man yeah
what have you been doing during the
quarantine in what is next in the in the
comedian world and in your world so like
it's obviously when it first hit it was
it was a big like punch in the gut for
just everybody doing anything it's
really scary the [__] to do but like
what what are you what's next like not
what are you avidly doing everyday like
what what are you thinking of what
where's your head at with what's next
right out the gate kovat corona happened
two shows got canceled my first show for
my band and another comedy show that we
had planned in April both got canceled
so okay got a rework what am i doing now
cuz I'm not allowed to be a stand-up
comedian so now I'm an Internet comedian
so what are we gonna do I have trust me
when I say this you're gonna want to be
following me on social media in the next
month or two no doubt give your ass real
quick we have it follow me on instagram
at crumb guzzler see our UMB underscore
GU zzl er same spelling on twitter but
an underscore and a crumb guzzler
underscore guzzler at crumb underscore
guzzler underscore you get it and then
Joseph creme on Facebook but I basically
went into content creation mode whether
or not I was gonna put it out that day
or not I just started writing and
recording things like a flippin maniac
and I've gone viral a good amount of
times in the past like half year a good
like six seven eight times and so I was
like okay I'm kind of resting on my
laurels without I have a new audience I
have a good whole new crop of people who
are just not introduced to me what am I
gonna do I have a backlog of videos on
my phone that would mail it it's it's
ridiculous dude it's just just
clips and clips that you have things
that I probably will never be able to
put on the internet with and be able to
go back to my family and look at them
straight face yes did I have a lot of
material that is ready to go I have been
saving up and writing so basically my
plan is this I'm going on a full social
media attack as soon as I have all this
stuff edited and everything set up kind
of like the format of one I do me and
stay in prison the band we're getting
our YouTube set up today I'm meeting
with Scottie after I leave here you guys
will be able to follow all that if you
check out my Instagram and my Twitter
you'll be directed to there but as soon
as I get done with this whole Co vid
stuff I'm just going to be releasing as
much content with as many content
creators and collaborating as much as I
can spending the money really making
stuff for you guys it's going to look
good and feel good like you're you're
going to look at it like nice and it's
gonna be hilarious because I'm hilarious
but then I'm gonna be working with
people like Max Payne if you guys love
max everybody loves him on the Internet
we're gonna be doing a lot of stuff I'm
gonna be putting on my own shows we're
gonna rent out venues we're gonna be
doing backyard shows hopefully saving up
and getting investors for the near
future to own our own venue we're gonna
be working on that but that's basically
it is I'm really really devoting my time
to it like it's actually my job no more
I go to work and then I sometimes post
funny stuff after my shift I am actively
working hard every day to put out
content like I've never done before I'm
really really trying to make it look
professional do it in a way that is
gonna shine back on me in a nice way and
that people will want to share and it'll
look good something to make me proud of
at least two because I've gone viral
I've done this before it's not anything
I haven't done I've I know how to make
my stuff pop and everything but it's
never really been anything I loved and
the comedy that I'm making right now is
comedy that I [__] love I enjoy
making it and I enjoy watching it it
pleased to be I'm just flushing myself
into it like I've never flushed into it
before I'm this is my this is what I'm
gonna do with my life there's no other
options that's basically it you'll be
able to follow me on Twitter Instagram
YouTube all that good shed and it's just
going to be flooding
okay I do as much as I possibly can I
think that's amazing all I can do really
yeah and then go into the stand-up shows
and we'll be putting shows like I always
have billed on probably once a month in
town and then I'll be going to open mics
all the time and people will be able to
see me doing that and all that [__]
yeah is that is there a constant open
mic in our area in Ellis County no never
there's not an open mic anybody
listening if you've ever had an urge to
open up little place or maybe go to a
place and say hey I want to be the
organizer of these things and I'm gonna
do it right that'd be great and reach
out to us we're thinking about setting
up one the problem is with a small town
is um making it sustainable to where you
have new people coming in every month
and new comedians coming in every month
so it most open mics are once a week
ours would probably be by monthly or
monthly but we're looking to set that up
too
me and Andy Kiggins have been talking
about that last time we did a show I'm
setting up a more monthly regular thing
you should get him on the show
eventually - have you already well so
technically we recorded my first five
episodes of this podcast I [__]
deleted
that's like that it was it was my main
[__] bro it was some it was some I saved
them sloppily on to my desktop in a
folder and then when I rerecorded some
more I just replaced the same files cuz
it was like file zero zero one it was
like do you want to replace the files
there it is this I'm like of course I do
and I just deleted them like some just
dorky [__] to do did you but hey Andy
what did you have like an actual like
outward burst of anger was it visible or
were you just like cuz I'm the type of
person I'm gonna be honest I don't have
I don't get you can like have sex with
like my mom I'm sorry mom
or like like slap me in the face not
that guy that's cool but like all like
accidentally like my lighter won't work
and I will freak out did you have like
an actual outburst of I don't know I
mean I'm trying to think back of like
how my reactions are when I'm just by
myself like because I'm definitely not
an aggressive person I don't like freak
out and don't act like crazy but
sometimes I will be overly dramatic as
[__] like I am no like my hands are on
my head and I'm
no see the whole room goes yeah so I
often question like I don't know if I'm
questioning God or just the ethos but
when something happens to me I am a face
to the sky why me person yeah are you
serious
why me what have I done to you I don't
know it's always you is you know to me
it is I'm doing that isackson thing but
I know it's there's a mirror I'm looking
at that's like you [__] you know you
did it like because it's always [__]
that you know you should have done a
little bit better like just throwing
files on my like I'm so excited to start
this podcast in the first five episodes
I just named ste - 0 0 1 through 5 God
you dick but so anyway yeah that was our
long rant but Andy was on this yeah and
I'm gonna get him back in here
so Andy Kagan's is an event promoter
he's like been doing his thing just
learning as he goes the same way that we
are we've worked a lot of shows together
he's a smart dude he's less often
yeah we've listed like he's the one who
got me booked with Cheney jingyang twins
hey Jones afro man I'm just rattled so I
found cool a few other people yeah a lot
of cool shows but dude the like yeah you
know I haven't caught up with him in a
while so as soon as I'm trying to manage
with a coronavirus like how many people
that have over like how to keep the
distance how to be respectful how to you
know my mom lives with me upstairs I'm
not trying to murder her yeah you know
because that's the thing is like is what
what a lot it's on a lot of our minds I
feel like but we're not really allowed
to talk about it it's like as a young
healing your mom well okay yes yes
Killer Moth Keep Calm
but but as young so we have kind of
cocky like I know I'm a pretty [__]
healthy [__] I'm yeah I like
supplements I workout like all these
things I'm like I'm gonna be fine if I
get it I feel pretty cocky about that
but like there's also so much part of me
that's like while my mom lives with me
yeah if I did get it she's dead
or you know she might not be she's
probably fine but she is older did you
see the Michael yo episode I don't Rogan
yeah bro his mom got it and beat it his
mom yeah he's a young man so you know
but the thing is
dude it's so what deficiency did you
hear about did you listen to that son
that's what we get it from the son
typically but this is 70% of people in
America are vitamin D or not that
vitamin D insufficient and then 30% of
people are too vitamin D deficient which
means like they [__] need it so
everybody go on Amazon right now thorn
it's $15 th o R and E you can get 5,000
vitamin D you can get a month supply of
honey for $15 or $12 or something go on
Amazon to it I'm fine it's like I don't
know I feel better even though yes I it
all makes me feel better all jokes aside
be as safe as you possibly can but
someone like me with an immune system
like I have I have done some wild stuff
I have units dude I don't even want us I
can't say in front of everybody do I
know what you could tell me about is
this time when I saw you got hit by a
[__] van remember that cool did I or
did I not land on my [__] feet I can
you okay let's uh we're getting up here
in time I think we could price send it
off around around here but I just love
to end on you tell the Jake saw me got
ran over when I was a kid okay so yeah I
got kicked out of it's gonna be a short
story but let me give just some kind of
backdrop to how cool we were when we
were younger because we were a very cool
young man in middle school so I got
kicked out of my middle school because
they wouldn't let me call my mom so I
went on a rampage through the middle
school tearing out all the phones from
each classroom as I went through the
school that got me kicked out I went to
Huntington middle school and I met this
young man sitting right across from us
now so we become friends we start
skating together to go into eighth grade
and everything we're full 2006 skinny as
jeans as you can imagine at a Michael
Locke haircut yes he sure did
My Chemical Romance t-shirts in full
effect random parts of our shirts just
cut off and wrapped around our ankles
and arms for no reason you know eyeliner
a lot a lot a lot
and so we're skating one day full --mode
up and there's this store that's kind of
like it kind of reminds me of a very New
York type feel where the store is like
on a triangle do you know what I mean
like that like you've seen buildings in
New York that are like this way or that
way yeah did that triangle building yeah
it's a store that's like that and you go
down one side of and there's an
embankment that goes into the street I'm
drinking the lovely beverage vault at
the time I don't know if you guys
remember $0.89 vaults very good I'm
drinking this like it's a like it's a
mountain Dew commercial I have my head
tilted back and I'm skating down the
embankment like it's just delicious and
I looked down and wouldn't you know a
big red truck there's this lady going
about 30 25 miles an hour in an SUV hits
me perfectly on the corner right where
like I looked like probably like a hood
ornament I was just like hugging the
front of her bumper and it popped me
into the air I did this weird 360
somehow my feet ended up in the wheel
well of the tire I feel like and I
landed and I landed on my feet I look up
Jake and gunner and is it Seth yeah I
look up at Jake and gunner and Seth and
they all have like food falling out of
their mouths like they're each in a
different state of shock one of them was
crying in the fetal position I feel like
it was it was scary
not really but they were shocked and I
look up and I'm just laughing that was I
was I didn't believe landed it bro I hit
my car and landed it 10 feet into the
air I did a little flip and I landed on
my feet and I looked up at them and I
just started cracking up and that pretty
much explains what my teenage years were
like in a nutshell just me getting hit
by cars landing on my feet and going it
takes another sip of alt and then I
didn't go to the hospital we didn't call
the cops we didn't call the ambulance I
actually went skateboarding later that
day and I continued my journey I well we
had a weird life I mean years was way
more savage than mine in different ways
but like it was weird like what we did
all time what were you saying
you were saying earlier about sometimes
like you were cool one of the things
that makes me feel great to this day is
when I still run into people from when
we were kids and they were like dude you
were so cool oh my god
I was that bad news bear kid like who
life was a mess I'm glad you enjoyed his
smoking cigarettes like in the lunchroom
and just being bad that was me and it
was great and I don't regret a second of
it it was awesome but to this day people
like you were cool and I'm like I was
traumatized I was really hurting inside
good well Joseph Crum I'm super glad
that you came over
I appreciate it out of it this was fun
dude yeah great times we could do this
again I'm glad that you came in here
like I texted you I was like bro
I think I'm gonna mention like I've been
uptight I just want to talk about where
the [__] were actually at I don't want
to pretend the coronavirus isn't real
surprisingly I feel like we were more
deeper than I thought we were gonna be
because normally there we could get
there this is the most serious I've been
for an extended period of time in a long
time I am normally all gay butts and
poop jokes so well you're in you're an
intellectual like I'm not putting that
on you like you have to show up to be
one you know [__] comedian I like
whenever I go on about stuff I'll be
talking about the meaning of life and
I'll tell people about Buddhism and then
I'll be like I'm just a [__] DJ
though like you so you can go there and
then I'm just a comedian it's your job
to see what people feel and it is my job
to see I think with comedians and DJs if
that makes any sense yeah it's just my
job to look around at things and be like
what the [__] yeah we're always we're
always looking at situations as a whole
where I was looking at things on a
linear longer than just now timeline
we're looking at not just our
perspectives but the whole rooms
perspectives it's a different way of
being than a lot of people I have a
challenge to people because I know that
a lot of these episodes squirt circle
around mental wellness and just you know
how can you help yourself the next time
like you feel like you're very certain
about something even if you don't feel
like you can genuinely get there in your
heart try to come full circle and go to
the other side of it and see if you can
relate to those people just see like I
think this is this and that's the way it
is just talk yourself into a circle and
see if you can find how they got to that
thinking like oh that's why you have
that belief on that thing just see if
you can do it and if not whatever cool I
oftentimes don't
people but if you can just see that's
all I'm saying you're really a man I
appreciate you coming on here I
appreciate talking to me good I died
three weeks later I'd be so all right
man one more time give him all your ass
Instagram it's gonna be at Crum does at
underscore Crum guzzler see our um be
underscore guzzler and same thing on
Twitter but underscore at the end at
under scrum underscore guzzler
underscore you guys will get it
hey and you'll be seeing some more
Joseph chrome around town if you are
from the area if you're one of those
listeners and be on the lookout for stay
in prison we're gonna be releasing a lot
of music and you guys will be able to
see us at your local coffee shop or a
punk rock bar in town we're looking
forward to all right listen here drink
some [__] water man love you